Hey guys, meet one of my new babies, Jedi.
Hey mama.
Here's the thing.
A lot of folks deserve to have a pet in their life.
They deserve to have the love of an absolute gorgeous, beautiful, cutie, cutie, cutie.
But they can't afford it.
You know why they can't afford it?
Because vet bills are no joke.
Because healthcare is real.
And because the reality is there just isn't a lot of support.
Now maybe you don't even want a cat.
You just love cats.
Let me tell you, the cat problem in Brooklyn is bonkers.
And unfortunately, the shelters are overrun.
So a lot of the cats that are out here on the street, they're not getting the care.
They're not getting the opportunity to find homes that they could.
The silver lining though, is that as with most problems,
there's somebody who's out here making it their business to try to fix it.
And that is Flatbush Cats.
They're literally building this solution right now
because they are opening a pro bono, non-profit, spay-neuter clinic in Brooklyn.
It's like weeks away from getting done.
But they need your help to get them doors open.
So I'm asking y'all to go to flatbushcats.org backslash build
to see how you can be a part of helping this issue.
Because everybody deserves to get the love of a Jedi.